A Finding Aid to the Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries Records, 1858-1969 (bulk 1919-1968), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries records
1858-1969
bulk 1919-1968
Archives of American Art
Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries
AAA.franrehg
Archival Resource Key
21.8 Linear feet
The Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries records measure 21.8 linear feet and are dated 1858-1969 (bulk 1919-1968). The records consist mainly of business correspondence with collectors, artists, museums and arts organizations, colleagues, and others. A small amount of Frank K. M. Rehns personal correspondence and a few stray personal papers of individual artists are interfiled. Also included are financial records, scrapbooks, printed matter, miscellaneous records, and photographs documenting most of the history of a highly regarded New York City art gallery devoted to American painting.
Historical Note
Frank K. M. Rehn (1886-1956), son of the marine painter Frank Knox Morton Rehn, after several years' experience as an employee of the Milch Galleries and as exhibition manager for the Salmagundi Club, opened his own art gallery in 1918. In its earliest years, the gallery operated as the Galleries of Frank K. M. Rehn. From the mid 1920s through the mid 1940s, the name used was Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries. As early as 1946, the gallery was referred to simply as Rehn Galleries. The gallery closed in 1981.
Throughout its existence, Rehn Galleries specialized in representing American painters. During the first five years Rehn's operation was a private gallery at 6 West 50th Street, New York City. Among the artists he first represented were older, established men such as J. Alden Weir, George Inness, Alexander Wyant, Theodore Robinson, Thomas Dewing, and John H. Twachtman. Occasionally, Rehn handled works by such luminaries of the period as Robert Henri, George Luks, and John Singer Sargent. Among the living artists affiliated with the gallery in its first years were Daniel Garber, Walter Griffin, Dodge MacKnight, and Robert Spencer. Rehn's most popular artist during this time was Childe Hassam, who sued for recovery of a painting that, although acquired by Rehn through a reputable dealer, had been stolen from Hassam's studio many years earlier.
Despite the newspaper publicity surrounding Hassam's lawsuit, the business was a successful venture almost immediately. Very early, a number of important collectors including Duncan Phillips, John Gellatly, John T. Spaulding, Albert McVitty, E. W. Root, and C. Vanderbilt Barton displayed confidence in Rehn's judgment and integrity, which enhanced his gallery's reputation and stature among both collectors and artists. In 1923, the gallery moved to 693 Fifth Avenue and began operating as Rehn Galleries, a commercial gallery in the same building that housed in a building that housed Kennedy and Company and the Bourgeois Galleries. At this time, Rehn hired an assistant, John C. Clancy (1897-1981), who had formerly been with Henry Reinhardt and Son and M. Knoedler.
The Rehn Galleries soon enjoyed a regular following among museum curators and collectors visiting from out of town. The gallery's roster of artists grew along with its reputation. Rehn focused almost exclusively on American painters, occasionally showing drawings and prints by artists who were primarily painters; notable exceptions were sculptor Mahonri Young and Henry Varnum Poor who, in addition to being a painter, was known for his work in ceramics. Among the painters eventually represented were: Peggy Bacon, George Bellows, Alexander Brook, Charles Burchfield, John F. Carlson, John Carroll, Howard Cook, Jon Corbino, Virginia Cuthbert, Andrew Dasberg, Sidney Gross, Edward Hopper, Alexander James, Irving Kaufmann, Yeffe Kimball, Leon Kroll, Peppino Mangravite, Reginald and Felicia Meyer Marsh, Henry Mattson, Henry Lee McFee, Kenneth Hayes Miller, Charles Rosen, Robert Riggs, Alexander Russo, Elizabeth Sparhawk-Jones, Eugene Speicher, Henry Strater, Richard Derby Tucker, Franklin C. Watkins, and Denny Winters.
In 1930, Rehn Galleries moved one block south to the Air France Building at 683 Fifth Avenue, and remained there for thirty years. John C. Clancy, Rehn's long-time assistant, became Gallery Director in 1953 after a stroke prevented Rehn from continuing to run his business in an active capacity. Eventually, Rehn's widow sold Clancy the gallery, which he continued to operate under varying names, including Rehn Gallery, Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries, Frank Rehn Gallery, and Rehn Galleries. From 1960 until 1966, The Rehn Galleries were at 36 East 61st Street from 1960 until 1966, when the gallery moved to a space formerly occupied by Kootz Gallery at 855 Madison Avenue, where it remained in business for another fifteen years.
Scope and Content Note
The Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries records measure 21.8 linear feet and are dated 1858-1969 (bulk 1919-1968). The records consist mainly of business correspondence with collectors, artists, museums and arts organizations, colleagues, and others. A small amount of Frank K. M. Rehn's personal correspondence and a few stray personal papers of individual artists are interfiled. Also included are financial records, scrapbooks, printed matter, miscellaneous records, and photographs documenting most of the history of a highly regarded New York art gallery devoted to American painting.
Series 1: Correspondence contains correspondence with artists, museums and arts organizations, collectors, colleagues, and others documents the workings of Rehn Galleries from its earliest days through 1968. A small amount of Frank K. M. Rehn's personal correspondence and a few scattered personal papers of individual artists are interfiled with the business correspondence.
Series 2: Financial Records includes banking, insurance, and investment records, tax returns and related documentation, miscellaneous financial records and paid bills. Among the insurance records are detailed monthly schedules listing paintings with titles, artists, and insurance values. Miscellaneous financial records include inventories of gallery stock, notes regarding business expenses and income, and receipt books recording incoming paintings. Also included are a small number of items concerning the personal business of Frank Rehn and John Clancy.
Five volumes of Scrapbooks (Series 3) contain clippings and a small number of exhibition catalogs documenting the activities of Rehn Galleries and many of its associated artists. Additional Printed Matter in Series 4 includes material relating to Rehn Galleries and its artists, as well as publications produced by Rehn Galleries. General, art-related printed matter consists of articles, auction catalogs, advertisements, and publications of various museums, arts organizations, and schools. There is also material about artists not affiliated with Rehn Galleries. Additional printed items concern miscellaneous subjects that are not art-related.
Series 5: Miscellaneous Records, includes artwork, lists and notes, and writings. Photographs in Series 6 are of people including artists represented by Rehn as well as several not affiliated with the gallery. Noticeably absent are likenesses of Frank Rehn and John Clancy. Photographs of works of art are by Rehn Galleries' artists and others. Reginald Marsh's photographs consist of family and personal photographs that were either given to Rehn Galleries or perhaps loaned for research use, and include views of Marsh from early childhood through later life, photographs of family and friends, and a small family album. Also included are photographs are of Marsh's childhood drawings.
Arrangement
Series 1: Correspondence is arranged alphabetically and Series 3: Scrapbooks is in rough chronological order. Series 2, and 4-6 are arranged in categories, as indicated in the Series Descriptions/Container Listing. Unless otherwise noted, items within each folder are arranged chronologically.
The collection is arranged into 6 series:
Missing Title
Series 1: Correspondence, 1858-1969, undated (Boxes 1-15; 14.4 linear ft.; Reels 5849-5869)
Series 2: Financial Records, 1919-1968, undated (Boxes 15-17; 2.6 linear ft; Reel 5869)
Series 3: Scrapbooks, 1919-1940 (Boxes 23-24; 0.6 linear ft.; Reels 5869-5870)
Series 4: Printed Matter, 1882-1969, undated (Boxes 18-20; 2.4 linear ft.; Reels 5870-5872)
Series 5: Miscellaneous Records, circa 1920-1968 (Boxes 20-21; 0.7 linear ft; Reel 5872)
Series 6: Photographs, 1871-1966, undated (Boxes 22, 24, OV 25; 1.0 linear ft.; Reel 5872)
Related Material
John Clancy interview by Paul Cummings, July 10, 1970. Oral History Program, Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution.
Samuel Adler Papers, 1902-1979. Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution. Contains a recording (1 cassette; untranscribed) of Beverly Chesler interviewing John Clancy about the history of Rehn Galleries, 1973; Samuel Adler is present and participates briefly in the interview.
Provenance
The Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries records were loaned by John Clancy for microfilming in 1959; in 1966, this same material was donated to the Archives. Mr. Clancy made subsequent gifts of additional gallery records in 1978 and 1981. In 1985, the Whitney Museum of American Art donated to the Archives correspondence with Edward Hopper that John Clancy had loaned the museum many years earlier. A death mask of George Luks received with the collection is on extended loan to the National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian Institution.
Restrictions on Access
The collection has been digitized and is available online via AAA's website.
Alternative Forms Available
The records of Frank K.M. Rehn Galleries in the Archives of American Art were digitized from 24 reels of microfilm. The records have been scanned in their entirety, and total 35398 images.
Art, Modern -- 20th century -- New York (State) -- New York; Scrapbooks; Sketchbooks; Works of art; Photographs; Art galleries, Commercial -- New York (State); Burchfield, Charles Ephraim, 1893-1967; Dasburg, Andrew, 1887-1979; Speicher, Eugene Edward, 1883-1962; Bartlett, Frederic Clay, 1873-1953; Bellows, George, 1882-1925; Coleman, Glenn O., 1887-1932; Cook, Howard Norton, 1901-1980; Cuthbert, Virginia, 1908-2001; Brook, Alexander, 1898-1980; Chappell, Warren, 1904-; Clancy, John C., 1897-1981; Marsh, Felicia Meyer, 1912-1978; Marsh, Reginald, 1898-1954; Mangravite, Peppino, 1896-; Orton, J. Robert; Pepper, Charles Hovey, 1864-1950; McFee, Henry Lee, 1886-1953; Melchers, Gari, 1860-1932; Hawthorne, Charles Webster, 1872-1930; Henri, Robert, 1865-1929; Gellatly, John, 1853-1931; James, Alexander, 1890-1946; Luks, George Benjamin, 1867-1933; Kroll, Leon, 1884-1974; Hopper, Edward, 1882-1967; Hopper, Jo N. (Josephine Nivison), 1883-1968; Young, Mahonri Mackintosh, 1877-1957; Winters, Denny Sonke, 1907-1985; Phillips, Duncan, 1886-1966; Tucker, Richard Derby, 1903-; Tucker, Allen, 1866-1939; Spalding, John T.; Russo, Alexander; Poor, Henry Varnum, 1887-1970; Strater, Henry, 1896-; Spruance, Benton, 1904-1967; Sparhawk-Jones, Elizabeth, 1885-1968
- Correspondence, A-Z, 1858-1969; undated; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 1-15; 14.4 linear feet; Reels 5849-5869)
  Scope and Contents note
  Correspondence, both business and personal, consists mainly of incoming letters with a smaller number of carbon copies or handwritten drafts of replies. Business correspondence is with artists, museums and arts organizations, collectors, colleagues, and others. Small amounts of the personal correspondence of Frank Rehn and John Clancy are scattered throughout this series. Also included are a few stray personal papers of individual artists that may have been enclosed with other correspondence or loans that the gallery never returned. Greeting cards (except for a few with original artwork that are with Series 5), printed enclosures, and a small number of photographs specifically relating to the contents of letters are filed here, as well. Also present are loose receipts for painting deliveries (two bound volumes of similar receipts are with Series 2) and receipts for art purchased by the gallery.
  Names listed under folder headings may not represent a comprehensive list of folder contents.
  - Abbott - Adams, 1920-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 13-47)
    Abbott, Jerre
    Abercorn Gallery
    Abdach, W. J.
    Abromson, Herman
    Abrons, Herbert L. and Mary G.
    ACA Gallery
    Accademia dei Virtuosi al Pantheon
    Achelis, Fritz
    Acheson, Mrs. Dean
    Acheson, George
    Ackerman, Theodore G.
    Adams, Abbie
    Adams, Davidson and Co., Inc.
    Adams, Mrs. Elbridge L.
    Adams, G. N.
  - Addison Gallery of American Art, Phillips Academy, 1940-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 48-133)
  - Addison Gilbert Hospital - Aichele, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 134-150)
    Addison Gilbert Hospital
    Adelphi College
    Adkins, Mrs. E. B.
    Adler, A. M.
    Adler, Charles, II
    Adler, Francis Heed
    Adler, Lee
    Adler, M. H.
    Agnew, Ella G.
    Aichele, Robert
  - Ainslie, George H./Ainslie Galleries, 1918-1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 151-242)
  - Air France - Albrecht, 1924-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 243-321)
    Air France
    Akron Art Institute
    Alabama Polytechnic Institute
    Alan Gallery
    Albany Institute of History and Art
    Albee, E. F.
    Albers, Carla
    Albert, Agnes
    Albrecht Gallery
    Albrecht, Walter E.
  - Albright Art Gallery/Buffalo Fine Arts Academy/Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 322-490)
  - Aldis - Altschuler, 1924-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 491-600)
    Aldis, Arthur
    Aldis, Mary
    Aldo Garzanti Editore
    Alexander and Alexander Insurance
    Alexander, Henry A.
    Alexander, Joan
    Alexander, Margaret
    Allan, Helen T.
    Allen, Agnes
    Allen, Arthur D.
    Allen, Mrs. C. R.
    Allen, Elsie
    H. L. Allen and Co.
    Allen, Harold
    Allen, James E.
    Allen, Mortimer P.
    Allen, Nellie Wright
    Allis, Mary
    H. V. Allison and Co., Inc.
    Allison, Stella
    Allstate Insurance Co.
    Allyn and Bacon, Inc.
    Allyn, Dorothea
    Alpern Foundation
    Altschul, Arthur G.
    Altschuler, Herbert
  - Amanel - American Consul, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 601-727)
    Amanel, Amoi
    America Designs, Inc.
    American Academy of Arts and Letters
    American Academy of Arts and Sciences
    American Airlines
    American Appraisal Company
    American Art and Artists
    American Art Association, Inc./American Art Galleries, Inc.
    American Art News Co., Inc.
    American Art Research Council
    American Artist
    American Artists Group, Inc.
    American Association of University Women
    American-British Art Center
    American Collector
    American Consul, Toronto
  - American Federation of Arts, 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5849, Frame 728-804)
  - American Federation of Arts, cont., 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5850, Frame 14-435)
  - American Friends of Hebrew University - Anuszkiewicz, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5850, Frame 436-547)
    American Friends of Hebrew University
    American Gallery
    American Girl
    American Heritage Publishing Co., Inc.
    American Institute of Arts and Letters
    American Institute of Decorators
    American Institute of Graphic Arts
    American Jewish Tercentenary
    American Library of Color Slides
    American National Committee of Engraving
    American National Exhibition in Moscow
    American Railway Express Company
    American Rescue Ship Mission
    American Society for Technion
    American Society of Painters, Gravers, and Sculptors
    American Surety Company of New York
    American Swedish Historical Museum
    American Telephone and Telegraph Co.
    American University
    American Watercolor Society
    American Weekly
    Ames, Elizabeth
    Ames, John L., Jr.
    Ames, Mrs. John W.
    Ames, Winslow
    Amherst College
    Amy Corporation
    Anderson, Elizabeth
    Anderson Galleries, Inc.
    Anderson, Margaret W.
    Anderson, Mr. and Mrs. Maxwell
    Andrews, Phoebe Warren
    Angers, Maude E.
    Anglo-Canadian Publishers Ltd.
    Anisman, C. Jacques
    Antin's Antiques and Reproductions
    Anuszkiewicz, Richard
  - A.P.F., Inc. - Art Collectors and Artists Association, 1920-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5850, Frame 548-641)
    A.P.F, Inc.
    Appelget, Thomas B.
    Appleton and Cox, Inc.
    Archdiocesan Service Corp.
    Archer, Mrs. Price
    Archives of American Art
    Arden Gallery
    Aragent Galleries
    Arkansas Arts Center
    Arkwell, Louise
    Arlington Art Galleries
    Armitage, Merle
    Armory Show 50th Anniversary Exhibition (See Henry Street Settlement)
    Arms, John Taylor
    Armstrong, A. J.
    Armstrong, George Alexander
    Arnold, Mrs. Harry B.
    Arnot Art Gallery
    Aron, Jerome I.
    Aronstamen, George C.
    Art Academy of Cincinnati
    Art Alliance (See Philadelphia Art Alliance)
    Art Appreciation Movement
    Art Association of New Orleans
    Art Association of Newport
    Art Book Publications, Inc.
    Art Center Association
    Art Center in la Jolla
    Art Club of Philadelphia
    Art Collectors and Artists Association
  - Art Dealers Association of America, Inc., 1962-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5850, Frame 642-1195)
  - Art Digest - Art in America, 1940-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Reel 5850, Frame 1196-1305)
    Art Digest
    Art Direction
    ARTgallery
    Art Gallery of Hamilton
    Art Gallery of Toronto
    Art in America
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1920-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5850, Frame 1307-1580)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, cont., 1920-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 14-43)
  - Art Institute of Zanesville, Ohio - Art News, 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 44-138)
    Art Institute of Zanesville, Ohio
    Art International
    Art Museum of the New Britain Institute
    Art News
  - Art Patrons of America - Artists Technical Research Institute, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 139-233)
    Art Patrons of America
    Art Quarterly
    Art Students League
    Art-Told Tales, Inc.
    Art: USA
    Art Voices
    Art Week
    Artist-Tenants Association
    Artists Equity Association
    Artists' Fellowship, Inc.
    Artists for Victory, Inc.
    Artists' Gallery
    Artists' Guild of Washington
    Artists League of America
    Artists' Packing and Shipping, Co.
    Artists Technical Research Institute
  - Arts - Arwin Galleries, 1923-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 234-328)
    Arts/Arts Magazine
    Arts and Antiques Show
    Arts and Crafts/Arts and Crafts Club of New Orleans
    Arts Club of Chicago
    Arts Coordinating Council
    Arts Guild of Williamsport
    Ahda Artz Gallery Ltd.
    Arwin Galleries
  - Associated American Artists - Astor, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 329-421)
    Associated American Artists
    Associated Artists of Syracuse
    Associated Libraries, Inc.
    Associated Press
    Association for the Help of Retarded Children, Inc.
    Association of Dealers in American Paintings
    Association of Oklahoma Artists
    Astor, John J.
    Astor, Vincent
  - Athena Gallery - N. W. Ayer and Son, Inc., 1940-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 422-496)
    Athena Gallery, Inc. (See also Mladinich, George)
    Atkins Museum of Fine Arts (See William Rockhill Nelson Gallery of Art)
    Atlanta Art Association/High Museum of Art
    Atlas Window Cleaning Company
    Atwater Kent Museum
    Atwood, John C., Jr.
    Audubon Artists
    R. C. Auletta and Co., Inc.
    Aument, Henrietta Sharom
    Avnet, Mr.
    Ayer, Charles M.
    N. W. Ayer and Son, Inc.
  - Babbage - Baker, 1922-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 498-590)
    Babbage, R. K.
    Babbot, Frank L., Jr.
    Babcock Gallery
    Babcock, Louise B.
    Backus, LeRoy M.
    Bacon, Peggy
    George Baer Gallery
    Bagley, Henry Walker and Nancy R.
    Bahnsen, C.
    Bailey, Edith
    Bailey, George
    Bainbridge, Charlotte W.
    Baird, Gordon
    Baird, Joseph A., Jr.
    Baker Collection Gallery
    Baker, Keith H.
    Baker, Marilyn
    Baker, Oliver and Sylvia
  - Balcom - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1919-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 591-673)
    Balcom, L. L. and S. T.
    Baldwin, Charles Lansing
    Balken, Edward Duff
    Ball, Mrs. George A.
    Ball State Teachers College
    Balliet, Ann
    Baltimore Municipal Museum
    Baltimore Museum of Art
  - Bancroft - Barns, 1918-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 674-789)
    Bancroft, F. S.
    Band, Charles S.
    Bandler, David B.
    Bangs, Mary Gray
    Bank of New York
    Bankers Trust Co.
    Barbee, Robert T.
    Barbee, Stanley N.
    Barclay, Elizabeth
    Barder, Al
    Bardley, Mrs. M. P.
    Baring, Edgar A., Jr.
    Barlandina, Jane
    Barn Gallery Associates, Inc.
    Barndollar, Clarence R.
    Barnes, Courtland D., Jr.
    Barnes, Mr. and Mrs. John
    John Barnes Foundation
    Matthew Barnes Trust
    Barney, Dorothea
    Barnhill, Marjorie
    Barns, Mrs. Robert
  - Barone - Barton, 1923-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 790-911)
    Barone, C. Gerald
    Barr, Alfred H., Jr.
    Barr, Norman
    Barrett, C. W.
    Barrett, Laura
    Barrett, Tom
    Barrington, Eugene
    Barron, Murray B.
    Barry, Ellen
    Barse, George R.
    Bartlett, Clay
    Bartlett, Marjorie
    Bartlett, Paul W.
    Barton, Cornelius Vanderbilt
    Barton, Frank
  - Basi - Beal, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 912-975)
    Basi, Albert
    Bassett, Jane Fowler
    Bassford, Wallace
    Basso, Lydia
    Bath, John C.
    Bauer, Mrs. Hebert
    Bauer, John
    Bauhan, William L.
    Bayard, Lucie
    Baylor University
    Bayne, S. G.
    Bayonne Jewish Community Center
    Bayroff, Mollie
    Bazner, Eleanor
    Beagary, H. Clinton
    Beal, Mrs. L. J.
  - Beal, Rebecca and James, 1941-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 976-1151)
  - Beard Art Gallery - Belton, 1918-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 1152-1267)
    Beard Art Gallery
    de Beaumont, Louis
    Beckman, Fredrick W.
    Beckwith, Mrs. Frank
    Beder, Robert M.
    Beede, Virginia S.
    Beer, Doris Riber
    Beers Bros. Co., Inc.
    Begien, Jeanne
    Beilin Gallery
    Belgian Government Information Center
    Belknap, William B.
    Bell, Natalie
    Bellows, George and Emma
    Belton, J. D.
  - Bemelmans - Bentley, 1926-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 1268-1308)
    Bemelmans, Ludwig
    Bement, A.
    Bender, William H., Jr.
    Bendiner, Alfred
    Benevy, Herbert
    Benner, Nolan P., Jr.
    Bennett, E. C.
    Bennett, Rhona
    Bennett, Thomas L.
    Benning, Margaret
    Bennington College
    Bentley, H. C.
  - Benton, William H., 1943-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 1309-1426)
  - Berg - Berkshire Publishing Co., 1925-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 1427-1521)
    Berg, G. L.
    Bering, Edgar A., Jr.
    Berkowitz, Rosalie
    Berkshire Art Center
    Berkshire Museum
    Berkshire Publishing Co.
  - Berlandina - Billingsley, B. H., circa 1922-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 1522-1579)
    Berlandina, Jane (See Howard, Jane Berlandina)
    Berley and Co., Inc.
    Berman, Harold
    Berman, L.
    Berman, Philip I.
    Berne, John H.
    Bernheimer and Zucker (See also Zucker, Harry T.; Hollander and Bernheimer)
    Bernstein, Robert
    Berresford Gallery
    Beseda, Ethel